directoryhound.co.uk 2017-12-16

# Phone Customer Services

**Privacy Policy**

We are committed to ensuring and protecting your privacy at any time you are on our website or communicate electronically with our personnel. Our Privacy Policy is contained below and provides a detailed explanation as to how we may use your personal information provided to us or any we collect through legal means.

**1\. Information We Collect from You**  
Data can be collected and processed when our website is in operation by you. The following are approved methods of collection:  
   1.1 If you register for information or complete a purchase, by filling out a form we can collect the information provided.  
   1.2 Traffic data, weblogs, location data, and any other communication can be collected. These details come from your visit to our site and any resource tools you use while on the site.  
   1.3 Any communication on our website or to personnel allows us to collect information.

**2\. Disclosing Your Information**  
   2.1 Personal information to third parties may not be disclosed:  
   2.2 We cannot sell any customer information to a third party.  
   2.3 Personal information cannot be offered to any member of our company, such as subsidiaries, holding companies and their subsidiaries.

**3\. Third Party Links**  
Links might be discovered on our site that belongs to third parties. Any third party website on our site has a privacy policy. You should check their terms. We do not accept liability or responsibility for their privacy policies, based on our lack of control over these third party links.

**4\. Access to Information**  
The Data Protection Act 1998 was established to govern online electronic communications. The act gives you access to any data we have about you. Contact information is given below, which should be used to gain details about information we hold on you. 

**5\. Communication**  
If you wish to speak to us about our service, please email us at [cs@phonecustomerservices.co.uk](mailto:cs@phonecustomerservices.co.uk) or call 0330 111 1025.

**Our Refund Policy**  
We want you to be completely satisfied with the service you receive, however if for any reason you feel we have not provided you with a satisfactory service, you may request a full refund for the cost of your call.

All refund requests are processed via email only, and will be made at the standard landline rate per minute for the entire duration of the call. To submit a refund request, please email us at the above address.

We will require the following:  
6\. Your name & telephone number  
7\. Your Address  
8\. A copy of the call entry on your next phone bill, stating the time of the call  
9\. The date of the call  
10.The number you dialled

Please note we will only process refund requests for calls made in the past 60 days. All refunds are made to the account holder on the telephone bill. Refund payments to be processed within 30 days of the submitted claim.
